[
    {
        "course": "biology",
        "institution": "jamb",
        "order": 7,
        "year": 1992,
        "question": "<img src=\"https://myschool.ng/storage/classroom/8118307374_bio19927and8.gif\" class=\"img-fluid\">",
        "explanation": null,
        "correctIndex": 0,
        "options": [
            "oesophagus",
            "trachea",
            "stomach",
            "intestine"
        ],
        "type": "objectives"
    },
    {
        "course": "biology",
        "institution": "jamb",
        "order": 8,
        "year": 1992,
        "question": "<img src=\"https://myschool.ng/storage/classroom/13530513690_bio19927and8.gif\" class=\"img-fluid\">",
        "explanation": null,
        "correctIndex": 2,
        "options": [
            "food vacuole",
            "nucleolous",
            "macronucleus",
            "contractile vacuole"
        ],
        "type": "objectives"
    },
    {
        "course": "biology",
        "institution": "jamb",
        "order": 19,
        "year": 1992,
        "question": "<img src=\"https://myschool.ng/storage/classroom/10824522952_bio199219and20.gif\" class=\"img-fluid\">",
        "explanation": null,
        "correctIndex": 0,
        "options": [
            "sweat gland",
            "sebaceous gland",
            "blood vessel",
            "nerve fibre"
        ],
        "type": "objectives"
    },
    {
        "course": "biology",
        "institution": "jamb",
        "order": 20,
        "year": 1992,
        "question": "<img src=\"https://myschool.ng/storage/classroom/20295977385_bio199219and20.gif\" class=\"img-fluid\">",
        "explanation": null,
        "correctIndex": 0,
        "options": [
            "2",
            "3",
            "4",
            "5"
        ],
        "type": "objectives"
    },
    {
        "course": "biology",
        "institution": "jamb",
        "order": 23,
        "year": 1992,
        "question": "<img src=\"https://myschool.ng/storage/classroom/2706146894_bio199223and24.gif\" class=\"img-fluid\">",
        "explanation": null,
        "correctIndex": 2,
        "options": [
            "cartilage",
            "ligament",
            "synovial fluid",
            "bone"
        ],
        "type": "objectives"
    },
    {
        "course": "biology",
        "institution": "jamb",
        "order": 24,
        "year": 1992,
        "question": "<img src=\"https://myschool.ng/storage/classroom/5412295164_bio199223and24.gif\" class=\"img-fluid\">",
        "explanation": null,
        "correctIndex": 2,
        "options": [
            "secrete a fluid which lubricates the joint",
            "attach muscles to the bones at the joint",
            "bend the bones at the joint",
            "hold the joint in place"
        ],
        "type": "objectives"
    },
    {
        "course": "biology",
        "institution": "jamb",
        "order": 29,
        "year": 1992,
        "question": "<img src=\"https://myschool.ng/storage/classroom/6765554060_bio199229and30.gif\" class=\"img-fluid\">",
        "explanation": null,
        "correctIndex": 2,
        "options": [
            "K",
            "L",
            "M",
            "N"
        ],
        "type": "objectives"
    },
    {
        "course": "biology",
        "institution": "jamb",
        "order": 30,
        "year": 1992,
        "question": "<img src=\"https://myschool.ng/storage/classroom/9471776762_bio199229and30.gif\" class=\"img-fluid\">",
        "explanation": null,
        "correctIndex": 0,
        "options": [
            "N",
            "M",
            "L",
            "K"
        ],
        "type": "objectives"
    },
    {
        "course": "biology",
        "institution": "jamb",
        "order": 35,
        "year": 1992,
        "question": "<img src=\"https://myschool.ng/storage/classroom/12178010016_bio199235and36.gif\" class=\"img-fluid\">",
        "explanation": null,
        "correctIndex": 3,
        "options": [
            "E",
            "F",
            "G",
            "H"
        ],
        "type": "objectives"
    },
    {
        "course": "biology",
        "institution": "jamb",
        "order": 36,
        "year": 1992,
        "question": "<img src=\"https://myschool.ng/storage/classroom/1353112349_bio199235and36.gif\" class=\"img-fluid\">",
        "explanation": null,
        "correctIndex": 1,
        "options": [
            "Algea",
            "Shark",
            "Tadpole",
            "Tilapia"
        ],
        "type": "objectives"
    }
]